tillys.com 2018-12-27

# Tilly's Privacy Policy

**Thank you for shopping at Tillys!**

At Tillys, our relationship with our customers is very important to us. That is why we work hard to protect your privacy and security. We prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose information and data when you use the Tillys web site and mobile applications (collectively, the “Sites”) and when you shop at our stores or otherwise interact with Tillys . We collect customer specific information in an effort to communicate details about our products, services, contests, and promotions and for other reasons described below.

Please know that Tillys will never disclose your personal information to any third party, unless it is necessary to provide you with products or services from Tillys or as otherwise described in our Privacy Policy.

**What Information We Collect:**

**Information You Give to Us**

When you place an order on the Sites, make a purchase in one of our [stores](https://www.tillys.com/store-list) , create an account, sign up for our loyalty program, sign up to receive e-mails or catalogues from us, enter a contest or sweepstakes, download our app, or otherwise interact with us, we may ask for your name, payment information, billing address, shipping address, phone number, mobile phone number, or e-mail address. The decision to provide this information is optional, however, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Sites. Some of this information may be stored in the form of a "cookie" on your computer. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer. Your Web browser may give you the option to refuse cookies. You may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Sites if you disable or delete cookies. We also may receive personal information through the use of social media web sites and services, mobile apps, or from other sources.

When you download or use the Tillys app, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. If you wish to stop these services, most mobile devices will allow you to turn off location services.

Information Collected Automatically

We automatically collect information regarding the actions you take on the Site (“Usage Data”). For example, each time you use the Sites we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Sites. This usage information may be associated with your username or other personal information. We use this information to help us understand how people use the Sites, and to enhance the services we offer. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Sites. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. Some of this information may also be stored using cookies, described above. We also may use other technologies on our website such as web beacons or javascript. Also, we may receive other information about you from third party sources, and we will add that to our account information, including as described below under “Combined Information.”

Information Collected from Third Parties

We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from Tillys, that website will submit to us your email address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. You may also choose to participate in a third party application or feature (such as one of our Facebook or Twitter applications or a similar application or feature) through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including Usage Data and personal information such as lists of your friends, "likes", comments you have shared, groups and location. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections" web page, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service. We may supplement the information we collect about you through social media and similar sites with such information from third parties in order to enhance our ability provide you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

How We Use Information and When We May Share and Disclose Information Generally

We use your personal information and Usage Data to fulfill your orders and to otherwise provide you with services that you request. We may also use your personal information to e-mail, text message (with your express written consent), mail, or otherwise send you information about new products and special features at Tillys. We may also offer you special promotions. If you prefer not to receive these e-mails, please indicate that when completing your order. For more information about managing your information choices, see “Your Information Choices” below.

Combined Information

We may combine your information, including Usage Data, with information from third parties in order to enhance our ability to communicate with you and provide you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.   In addition, from time to time, we may establish relationships with other people or entities whom we believe to be trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours. In this context, we may disclose to third parties your Usage Data and other personal information that you provide to us, so long as combined and used in aggregate form and in a manner that does not identify you. 

Cookies

Cookies are small files saved to your computer. Cookies can be used for a number of important purposes. For example they allow us to distinguish you from other users on our website which help us to provide you with a great online experience as well as improve our website. Cookies allow us to gauge where our visitors come from (i.e. Google), recognize and count the number of visits to our site, as well as how visitors move around the site. Cookies help us to improve not only the way our website works, but to ensure you find what you’re looking for easily as well. 

Tillys uses persistent cookies, either directly or indirectly through one of our third party providers. We also use other tracking technology such as pixel tags or web beacons. These Technologies assist us with your requests, and make your browsing experience easier (i.e. by remembering which language you prefer) this way you enjoy a seamless experience.  Persistent cookies assist us with understanding how you use our website. It also allows us to target you with specifically tailored advertising based on your visit(s) along with carry out business analytics, other statistic activities and traffic. 

Depending on your browser’s settings, your computer may alert you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. You can choose to accept the cookie or not or you can choose to turn off cookies via your browser’s settings. If you do decided to turn off your cookies you may not have access to some of the features that make your experience easier and some services may not function properly.

If you choose to participate in our use of cookies but later change your mind you can simply opt out at any time by going through your browser settings. Your browser settings will also allow you to delete the cookies that have already been set and change your browser settings to block all or part of any further cookies.

Mobile Application

The collection and means of collecting information through any currently existing or future App are previously discussed in this policy. The sharing of any information is also previously discussed in this policy.

In addition, by using the App you may be asked for permission to access data on your mobile device, such as photos. We will only access this data with your consent. Please note that some functions of the App are only available if you allow access to requested content.

You are able to opt-out of certain functions of the App by changing the settings on your mobile device. For specific instructions, please refer to the instructions provided for your mobile device.

Security and Credit Card Safety

Protecting the safety of your credit card information is important to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is a highly sophisticated method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our Sites' servers.

To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your Web browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or “Address” line of your Web browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https".

We use industry-standard security techniques on the Sites to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you on the Sites. When you access your account information or transmit personally identifiable data to the Sites, that information is stored on servers that the Sites has attempted to secure from unauthorized access or intrusion. That said, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Sites, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Sites, and you do so at your own risk.

**We urge our customers to be cautious with personal and account information.**  
If you think that you may have disclosed your personal or account information in error, or that you have been a victim of fraudulent account activity, please contact your bank and/or credit card company immediately. You may also wish to contact a credit reporting agency.

**Your Information Choices**

We will occasionally send members of our distribution list information and valuable offers by mail or e-mail, or text message if you have expressly agreed to receiving text messages. You may unsubscribe from our marketing lists at any time. To unsubscribe from receiving marketing e-mails, please click on the appropriate link at the bottom of any marketing e-mail from Tillys or by signing into your account on the Sites and changing your e-mail preferences. If you have opted in to receive text messages from us, you can unsubscribe from receiving text messages at any time by: (1) replying to the text message with the word "STOP"; (2) sending the text message "STOP" to 38714; or (3) contacting us. You can also contact us directly to unsubscribe from mail, e-mail, or text communications by e-mailing us at customerservice@tillys.com.

Personal Information You Make Available to Others

By using the Sites, you may make certain of your personal information available to others. For example, when you post a comment or a photo on the Sites other users may see your name, the city you live in and other information that you choose to make available to others.

Service Providers

From time to time, we may contract with other businesses whom we believe to be trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours to perform services for or on behalf of Tillys (“Service Providers”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies or other tracking technology in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using personal information other than as specified by Tillys.

Advertising & Do Not Track

We may allow third-party companies to serve ads or collect certain information about you when you visit the Sites. These companies may use browsing information (e.g., click stream information, Web browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to the Sites and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about products and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or other technology to collect this information.

Our systems do not recognize Do Not Track (DNT) signals from browsers. DNT is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. However, many third party services that collect this type of information permit you to opt out through a separate system. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising from participating third parties providers, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) . In addition, please see the Your Information Choices section to learn how to manage what marketing or other information you receive directly from us.

In addition, Tillys uses Google Analytics to monitor activity on the Sites. To learn how Google Analytics collects and processes data, please visit: “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” located at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.tillys.com/customer-service/privacy-security/www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).

Other Transfers

We may share personal information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Tillys. If Tillys is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer personal information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Tillys cooperates with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose personal information and any other information about you if we believe it is reasonably necessary to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property, or rights of Tillys, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

Be Careful Sharing Information with Others

Please remember that when you share information with third parties or on any public area of the Sites, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications. You are solely responsible for keeping your login credentials and any other account numbers or access codes secure.

Links to Other Web Sites

Our Sites may contain links to other web sites, or allow others to send you such links. A link to a third party’s web site does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party web sites. You access such third-party web sites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party web site before providing any information to the web site.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Sites and communications are intended for those who are at least 13 years old and older. Tillys will not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If a parent, guardian, or anyone else becomes aware of personal information we have collected from an individual under the age of 13, please contact us at (866) 484-5597 or via email at customerservice@tillys.com.

Minors in California may remove, or request and obtain removal of content or information that they have publically posted on the Sites by e-mailing us at customerservice@tillys.com. Please note that most of the user content that appears on the Sites is stored and controlled by third party providers. As a result, complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information may not be possible.

Your California Privacy Rights

This Policy describes how we may share your information for marketing purposes. You may contact us with any questions and, to the extent applicable, to request once a calendar year a list of third parties to whom we may disclose information for their own marketing purposes and the categories of information we may disclose.

Use of the Sites Outside of the United States

Please be aware that your personal information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. Please be advised that we do not intentionally direct the Sites or offer goods or services to residents of countries outside of the United States.  We process and store information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using the Sites, you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your personal information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, your dealings with Tillys, wish to unsubscribe from any of our marketing lists, or want to update your information, you can contact us at:

Customer Service  
Tillys  
10 Whatney  
Irvine, CA 92618  
customerservice@tillys.com  
1-866-4TILLYS

Privacy Policy Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Sites or in another manner as appropriate. Those changes will go into effect on the “Revised” date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to access or use the Sites, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy. We recommend that you frequently check the website for recent changes.

Revised: May 26, 2018
